[{"answer": "You know, actually, (INAUDIBLE) this morning, because when I woke up this morning, for some reason, something was telling me not to go to work, like something told me to call the company and tell them I couldn't come in.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "I was coming up from the Green Line.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "What did you see?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Would you think that's probably right?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "No, my brother is -- you know, he's such a loving uncle to his nieces and nephews.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Did anybody at any stage -- did your brother ever say he had a problem with this guy?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think this is a referendum on guns in America.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What do you feel about guns in America right now?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Fine.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "IULIANI, FORMER NYC MAYOR (via telephone): How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think these -- the situations are not the right situations to pick to debate gun control, either this one or the one that took place a couple weeks ago.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "What do you think should happen?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "No, but I think it was not the most tasteful joke.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Be honest, Rudy, do you think that was a little below the belt?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Oh, well, I'm only apprehensive because of the storm.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Are you excited about the convention, Rudy, or are you slightly apprehensive?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Yes, he gave up.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Were you as shocked as everybody else seems to have been when he threw the towel in?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Marion Jones never failed a drug test and she is known as one of the great cheaters of our time.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "What's the informed reaction?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a journalist.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Do you think, Christine, there's any doubt Lance Armstrong was a cheat?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "No, I love big challenges.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "You don't do things by halves, do you?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I think it's too early to know, quite frankly.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do you think either Romney or Obama has been courageous enough with their plan for the economy?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Yes, I think it's an interesting idea.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "-- and taking a little wager that the American will reward them for that patriotic hit on their balance sheet by going out and buying more products?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, you know, when we launched the Apple Store, Steve knew that for Apple to win, it was going to win on innovation.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "When you were given the task by Steve Jobs of creating the Apple Store, what was the philosophy that you really wanted to create?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "You had hundreds and hundreds and hundreds, as I recall.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Now how many failures did you have to go through first?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "When we're not on set, we're often in a park just putting it all out there.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Awkward to do that on camera, or are you two just such shameless exhibitionists that it just came naturally?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Not when we first met, no.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Did you know about this when you met?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Well, my only obsession that was stronger than that was working.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "How did you, in the end, get the self-determination to get yourself out of it?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "In California specifically.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Is this true, that you waited for same sex marriage to be endorsed before you took the plunge yourselves?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Yeah, we're liberals.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Are you both, I'm guessing, Obama supporters?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Will it --", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "ORGAN: What does the prospect of a Romney presidency do to you?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Any respect you like.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "In what respect?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "I'll tell you, I read in \"Vanity Fair\" how Putin dealt with some of his adversaries in Russia.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "What do you think of your country?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I didn't.", "docId": "120824pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Be honest?", "qSentId": 680}]